rvforum.net 2018-11-05

# The RV Forum - Privacy Policy

The RV Forum - Privacy Policy
Effective date: June 02, 2018
The RV Forum ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.rvforum.net website (the
"Service").
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of
personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the
collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in
this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our
Terms and Conditions, accessible from http://www.rvforum.net
Definitions
        Service
        Service is the http://www.rvforum.net website operated by The RV Forum
        Personal Data
        Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those
        data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come
        into our possession).
        Usage Data
        Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service
        or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
        Cookies
        Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
        Data Controller
        Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in
        common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in
        which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.
        For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal
        Data.
        Data Processors (or Service Providers)
        Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who
        processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.
        We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data
        more effectively.
        Data Subject (or User)
        Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of
        Personal Data.
Information Collection and Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and
improve our Service to you.

Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable
information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally
identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
•   Email address
•   Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This
Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g.
IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time
and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other
diagnostic data.
Tracking Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and
hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique
identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device.
Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track
information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being
sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our
Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
•   Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
•   Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and
    various settings.
•   Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
•   Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements
    that may be relevant to you and your interests.
Use of Data
The RV Forum uses the collected data for various purposes:
•   To provide and maintain our Service
•   To notify you about changes to our Service
•   To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do
    so

•    To provide customer support
•    To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
•    To monitor the usage of our Service
•    To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection
Regulation (GDPR)
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), The RV Forum legal basis for collecting
and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal
Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.
The RV Forum may process your Personal Data because:
•    We need to perform a contract with you
•    You have given us permission to do so
•    The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
•    To comply with the law
Retention of Data
The RV Forum will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the
purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the
extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to
retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal
agreements and policies.
The RV Forum will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is
generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen
the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to
retain this data for longer time periods.
Transfer of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on —
computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental
jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note
that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information
represents your agreement to that transfer.
The RV Forum will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated
securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data
will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place
including the security of your data and other personal information.

Disclosure of Data
Disclosure for Law Enforcement
Under certain circumstances, The RV Forum may be required to disclose your Personal Data
if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court
or a government agency).
Legal Requirements
The RV Forum may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to:
•    To comply with a legal obligation
•    To protect and defend the rights or property of The RV Forum
•    To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
•    To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
•    To protect against legal liability
Security of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission
over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use
commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
"Do Not Track" Signals
We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your
web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.
You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your
web browser.
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection
rights. The RV Forum aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete,
or limit the use of your Personal Data.
If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be
removed from our systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
         The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
         Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your
         Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to
         perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.

        The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if
        that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
        The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal
        Data.
        The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the
        processing of your personal information.
        The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the
        information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used
        format.
        The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent
        at any time where The RV Forum relied on your consent to process your personal
        information.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use
of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection
authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service
Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to
assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our
behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
        Google Analytics
        Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports
        website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our
        Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected
        data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
        You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google
        Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on
        prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing
        information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
        For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google
        Privacy Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Advertising
We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support
and maintain our Service.

         Google AdSense DoubleClick Cookie
         Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's
         use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users
         based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet.
         You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising
         by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page:
         http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a
third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to
review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or
practices of any third party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 16 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age
of 16. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us
with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal
Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that
information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by
posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the
change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this
Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
•    By email: admin1@rvforum.net
